

Trần Huyền Chinh

I have been working as a purchasing officer for more than 2 years. Through my career, I have achieved purchasing skills and understood the product market so I can bring a lot of value to the company such as increasing profits and contributing to long - term development.



An Binh City, Pham Van Dong, Nam Tu Liem, Ha Noi, Viet Nam in



Work Experience

Purchasing Officer • HUY HOANG EQUIPMENT IMPORT EXPORT JOINT STOCK

Main responsibilities:

- Receive demand from the sales manager and make a plan to purchase equipment
- Negotiate and make contracts with suppliers
- Plan quotation for each order to report to the manager
- Manage and track import orders, coordinate with other departments to ensure order progress
- Collect and check documents such as PL, INV, CO/CQ for each order
- Check freight rates from each forwarder
- Take responsibility and update reports on working process as well as import-related issues
- Management and storage of import and export documents.

October 2022 - Present

Purchasing Officer • TRUONG PHAT CONSTRUCTION DEVICE COMPANY LIMITED

Main responsibilities:

- Receive demand from Sales manager and make a plan to purchase equipment
- Negotiate with international suppliers in line with market needs
- Plan quotation combined with Salesmen
- Collect and check documents such as PL, INV, CO/CQ for each order
- Check freight rates from each forwarder
- Solve shipping problems

April 2021 - July 2022

Teaching assistant • Lear English with Ms. Hoang Xuan

Main responsibilities:

- Support the teacher to manage the classroom
- Introduce and advise students' parents about each course

- Compose topics and translate texts

ACTIVITIES

May 2020 - March 2021

Staff • MID-AUTUMN FESTIVAL FOR CHILDREN

- Collaborate with other staffs to arrange and prepare the necessary equipments
- Guide the volunteers to donate blood

January 2019 - February 2019

Education



2019 - 2022

FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY

International Commerce

Skills

Language

- Collaboration Skills
- Negotiation
- Advise Students
- ERP
- Office Information Technology

• English - Professional

Powered by CakeResume